{
    "subject": "resource/Dori_Caymmi",
    "predicate": "property/instrument",
    "object": "resource/Guitar",
    "human_readable": "Dori Caymmi plays the Guitar.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.986522376537323,
            "question": "Is the guitar an instrument that Dori Caymmi plays?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.986080527305603,
            "question": "Does Dori Caymmi play the guitar?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9760865569114685,
            "question": "Name a musical instrument played by Dori Caymmi."
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9299140572547913,
            "question": "What instrument does Dori Caymmi play?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9165734052658081,
            "question": "Is Dori Caymmi a musician?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8293238878250122,
            "question": "What musical instrument is associated with Dori Caymmi?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7596955895423889,
            "question": "What is Dori Caymmi known for playing?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7513934373855591,
            "question": "Dori Caymmi's musical talent includes playing what?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6629552245140076,
            "question": "What instrument is mentioned in relation to Dori Caymmi?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5604087710380554,
            "question": "What skill does Dori Caymmi possess?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Dori Caymmi plays the Guitar.",
            "html": "dbpedia_630_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What instrument is mentioned in relation to Dori Caymmi?",
            "html": "dbpedia_630_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Dori Caymmi's musical talent includes playing what?",
            "html": "dbpedia_630_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is Dori Caymmi known for playing?",
            "html": "dbpedia_630_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_630_113.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_630_114.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_630_122.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_630_15.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_630_17.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_630_26.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_630_37.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_630_53.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_630_65.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_630_77.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here is the answer in the form of a structured JSON format:\n\n```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe information in the documents supports the triple that Dori Caymmi plays the guitar. According to several articles, Dori Caymmi is described as a guitarist-singer-songwriter and his music is distinguished by his distinctive, emotive playing style on the guitar."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents mention that Dori Caymmi is a master of the guitar and performs with it, supporting the statement that he plays the guitar."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\n     \"output\": \"yes\"\n   }"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "The Least Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}